## Srinivasan Chakkarapani

## **Product Designer**

## **Summary**

A passionate full spectrum product designer with 4+ years of experience in solving complex problems through digital products. Having designed and shipped products across different sectors, I'm an advocate for functional, aesthetic and user-centered products which has a meaningful impact on people's life solving a need.

## **Professional Experience**

#### **Product Designer | NortonLifelock**

November 2020 - Present

Working on the interaction and visual design of core mobile experiences of Norton's flagship cybersecurity product, Norton 360.

#### **User Experience Design Intern | Google**

June 2019 - September 2019

Designed and shipped the first version of the design system for Google Ad Manager. Primarily worked on the component library from audit to shipping a library of reusable components for designers in the team. Worked with the visual design lead, senior interaction designers to define the component design process.

#### Interaction Designer | Zeta

February 2018 - August 2018

Improved the visual design and user experience of the leave travel allowance program in Zeta optima. Worked as sole designer for two stealth mode products focusing on digitising the tax benefits for employers & employees on web and mobile platforms by ideating, conceptualizing and designing the product.

#### **Product Designer | Zoho Corporation**

December 2015 - January 2018

Designed and shipped the first version of Zoho Sheet product on mobile platforms as the primary product designer. I worked on designing the application for iOS and Android platforms from ideating features, wireframing to high fidelity mocks and framing a design system. The shipped product currently has ~100k users with an average rating of 4.0 and above on the App Store and Play Store.

#### **Product Designer | Holachef**

June 2015 - December 2015

Designed and shipped the second version of the iOS and Android applications for the company. Collaborated with the product design lead to redesign the primary web product. The applications improved the efficiency by ~21%, measured in terms of user engagement and conversion rate.

#### www.srinivasan.design

tcsreeni93@gmail.com

+1 312-973-6557

#### **Education**

## Masters in Human Computer Interaction

DePaul University, Chicago

# **Bachelors in Computer Science** & Engineering

SASTRA University, India

#### **Skills**

User Research

Wireframing

Interaction Design

Visual Design

Prototyping

Motion Design

**Usablity Testing** 

**Design Systems** 

Information Architecture

**Product Strategy** 

Competitive Analysis

A/B Testing

Conversation Design

#### **Tools**

### Wireframing

Balsamiq

Axure RP

#### Design

Figma

Sketch

Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator

#### **Prototyping**

Principle

Adobe After Effects

ProtoPie

#### **Development**

HTML

css

**JavaScript**